Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files P-T, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files A
  - Subject Files P
    - Phillips, Alberta (Box A-95, Folder 25)
      One print has cut-out rubylith transparency affixed to image recto.
    - Phillips, Arthur A. (Box A-95, Folder 26)
    - Phillips, Audrey (Box A-95, Folder 27)
    - Phillips, Basil G. (Box A-95, Folder 28)
    - Phillips, Berllina (Box A-95, Folder 29)
    - Phillips Bros. (Box A-95, Folder 30)
      One velox print.
    - Phillips, Carl Hudson (Box A-95, Folder 31)
    - Phillips, Carolyn (Box A-95, Folder 32)
    - Phillips, Carrie (Box A-95, Folder 33)
    - Phillips, Cecil (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 34)
    - Phillips, Channing (Box A-95, Folder 35)
    - Phillips, Claudia (Box A-95, Folder 36)
    - Phillips, Curtis (Box A-95, Folder 37)
    - Phillips, Cynthia (Box A-95, Folder 38)
    - Phillips, Clifford (Box A-95, Folder 39)
    - Phillips, David L. (Box A-95, Folder 40)
    - Phillip, Daivad (Box A-95, Folder 41)
    - Phillip, David W. (Box A-95, Folder 42)
    - Phillip, Morris Incorp. (Box A-95, Folder 43)
      Photographer if identified: Circulation Experti
    - Phillips, Dawad (Box A-95, Folder 44)
    - Phillips, Doris (See Bklyn Home for The Aged) (Box A-95, Folder 45)
    - Phillilps, Earl (Box A-95, Folder 46)
      Photographer if identified: Douglas Meany Studio
    - Phillips, Edward (Box A-95, Folder 47)
      Photographer if identified: Robert L. Haggins
    - Phillips, Elizabeth Murphy (See Robert Kennedy) (Box A-95, Folder 48)
    - Phillips, Erie (Box A-95, Folder 49)
    - Phillips, Esther (Box A-95, Folder 50)
      Photographer if identified: M Associates
    - Phillips, Fitzgerald (Box A-95, Folder 51)
    - Phillips, Foster J. (Box A-95, Folder 52)
    - Phillips, George (Box A-95, Folder 53)
    - Phillips, Gloria (Box A-95, Folder 54)
    - Phillips, Irma (Box A-95, Folder 55)
    - Phillips, Janice R. (Box A-95, Folder 56)
    - Phillips, John (Box A-95, Folder 57)
    - Phillips, John L., Jr. (Box A-95, Folder 58)
    - Phillips, John M. (Capt.) (Box A-95, Folder 59)
      Print is badly darkened and is giving off a chemical odor.
      Photographer if identified: New York Fire Department
    - Phillips, Joyce (Mrs.) (See Susan Gordon) (Box A-95, Folder 60)
    - Phillips, Karen (Box A-95, Folder 61)
    - Phillips, Larry L. (Rev.) (Box A-95, Folder 62)
      Black and white Polaroid print.
    - Phillips, Lillian (Box A-95, Folder 63)
    - Phillips, Linnette (Box A-95, Folder 64)
    - Phillips, Marishka (Box A-95, Folder 65)
    - Phillips, Mary and Phillips, Myrtle (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 66)
    - Phillips, Neil F., II (Box A-95, Folder 67)
    - Phillips, Norris (Box A-95, Folder 68)
    - Phillips, P. Bertrand (Box A-95, Folder 69)
    - Phillips, Pauline (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 70)
    - Phillips, Ralph L. (Box A-95, Folder 71)
    - Phillips, Reuben (Box A-95, Folder 72)
      Photographer if identified: James J. Kriegsmann
    - Phillips, Robert (Box A-95, Folder 73)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos
    - Phillips, Robert A. (Box A-95, Folder 74)
    - Phillips, Rosie (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 75)
    - Phillips, Royce (Box A-95, Folder 76)
      Also three velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Medgar Evers College, Board of Education/City of New York
    - Phillips, Sam (Box A-95, Folder 77)
    - Phillips, Sandra Reaves (Box A-95, Folder 78)
    - Phillips, Samuel W. (Box A-95, Folder 79)
    - Phillips, Sandra and Lacy (Box A-95, Folder 80)
      Also two velox prints.
    - Phillips, Sarah (Box A-95, Folder 81)
    - Phillips, Tina (Box A-95, Folder 82)
    - Phillips, Trevor (Box A-95, Folder 83)
      One cut-out photocopy of an illustration.
    - Phillips, Tyrone (Box A-95, Folder 84)
    - Phillips, Victor B. also Phillips, Warren (Box A-95, Folder 85)
    - Phillips, Wm. (Box A-95, Folder 86)
    - Phillips, Wm. H. (Dr.) (Box A-95, Folder 87)
      Photographer if identified: F.J. Higgins
    - Philpot, Christine (Box A-95, Folder 88)
      Photographer if identified: Bradford Bachrach
    - Philpotts, Randolph (Box A-95, Folder 89)
    - Phipp, Edith (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 90)
    - Phipps, Charles C. (Box A-95, Folder 91)
    - Phipps, Edgar E. (Box A-95, Folder 92)
    - Phipps, Henry (Box A-95, Folder 93)
    - Phipps, Howard, Jr. (Box A-95, Folder 94)
    - Phipps, Howard (Mrs.) (See Alice Arrington) (Box A-95, Folder 95)
    - Phipps, Kenneth (See Inactive File near cuts) (Box A-95, Folder 96)
    - Phipps, Michael (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 97)
      Ms. notation on image recto.
    - Phipps, Naomi (Box A-95, Folder 98)
    - Phipps, Patricia (Box A-95, Folder 99)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, James Gilbert
    - Phipps, Yvonne C. (Box A-95, Folder 100)
    - Phipps, William A. (Box A-95, Folder 101)
      Photographer if identified: New York Port of Embarkation
    - Phoenix House (Box A-95, Folder 102)
    - Phoenix, Joseph D. (Box A-95, Folder 103)
      Cut-out segment of black and white Polaroid print mounted to heavy board.
    - Phoenix, Naomi (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 104)
    - Phoenix, Ray (Box A-95, Folder 105)
    - Phoenix Singers (Box A-95, Folder 106)
    - Phoenix, Viola (Box A-95, Folder 107)
      Photographer if identified: Herbert Hawkins, Glamour Pix, Dummett, James C. Campbell
    - Phox, Gloria (Box A-95, Folder 108)
    - Piaza, Carol (Box A-95, Folder 109)
    - Piccoli, Leonard R. (Box A-95, Folder 110)
      Also one typescript release on three leaves.
    - Pickens, Eugene (Box A-95, Folder 111)
      Photographer if identified: Jan Jachniewicz
    - Pickens, Harriett (Box A-95, Folder 112)
    - Pickens, James, Jr. (Box A-95, Folder 113)
    - Pickens, Joann (Box A-95, Folder 114)
    - Pickens, William (Box A-95, Folder 115)
    - Pickens, Wm. (Box A-95, Folder 116)
    - Pickens, Wm. III (Box A-95, Folder 117)
      Photographer if identified: Martar Photo
    - Pickets, Jerry (Box A-95, Folder 118)
    - Pickett, Bill (Box A-95, Folder 119)
      Photographer if identified: P.A. Reuter Photos Ltd./London
    - Pickett, Carol (Box A-95, Folder 120)
    - Pickett, Cheryl (Box A-95, Folder 121)
    - Pickett, Delores (Box A-95, Folder 122)
      Photographer if identified: Tommy Comer, Dalman James Jr., Cecil Layne
    - Pickett, Jerome (Box A-95, Folder 123)
    - Pickett, Jessica (Box A-95, Folder 124)
    - Pickett, Madeline (Box A-95, Folder 125)
    - Pickett, Stephen (Box A-95, Folder 126)
    - Pickett, Wilson (Box A-95, Folder 127)
      Number of Prints: 17
    - Pickney, Ebony (Box A-95, Folder 128)
    - Pickney, Emma (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 129)
    - Picnic (Box A-95, Folder 130)
      Photographer if identified: Coreen Simpson
    - Picon, Molly (Box A-95, Folder 131)
    - Picott, Rupert (Box A-95, Folder 132)
      Photographer if identified: Brodnax Studio
    - Picott Family (Box A-95, Folder 133)
    - Pieces of a Dream (Box A-95, Folder 134)
    - Pierce, Billy (Box A-95, Folder 135)
      Photographer if identified: Norman Frederick, Billy Pierce
    - Pierce, Burton (Box A-95, Folder 136)
      Photographer if identified: Whitestone Studio
    - Pierce, C.E. (Rev.) (Box A-95, Folder 137)
    - Pierce, Deborah (Box A-95, Folder 138)
    - Pierce, Elijah (Box A-95, Folder 139)
    - Pierce, George (Box A-95, Folder 140)
    - Pierce, J.A. (Dr.) (Box A-95, Folder 141)
    - Pierce, John (Box A-95, Folder 142)
    - Pierce, Larry (Box A-95, Folder 143)
    - Pierce, Lawrence (Box A-95, Folder 144)
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, Studio of The New York Times, James Gilbert, David McAdams, Ace Creative Studios, Ira Mandelbaum
      Number of Prints: 23
    - Pierce, Marilyn (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 145)
    - Pierce, Marylynn G. (Box A-95, Folder 146)
    - Pierce, Mona (Box A-95, Folder 147)
      Photographer if identified: Dummett, Harris Photo, Burley, Rapid News Photo, Bro. David McAdams
    - Pierce, Ponchita (Box A-95, Folder 148)
    - Pierce, Samuel Riley (Box A-95, Folder 149)
      Also one velox print. Also one halftone negative.
      Photographer if identified: Ly Benson's Photo Service/Kenneth Hodges, Harris Photo, A. Hansen, James Gilbert, Robert L. Haggins, Layne's Studio, James C. Campbell
      Number of Prints: 22
    - Pierrepointe, Reginald (Box A-95, Folder 150)
      Photographer if identified: Vandel Nichols
    - Pierre, Albert C. (Box A-95, Folder 151)
    - Pierre, Fannie (on picture with Shavers, Blanche) (Box A-95, Folder 152)
    - Pierre, Fannye (Box A-95, Folder 153)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, George West, D&G Timmons, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, David McAdams
    - Pierre-Noel, Lois Jones (Dr.) (Box A-95, Folder 154)
    - Pierce, Lawrence (Judge) (Box A-95, Folder 155)
    - Pierrepointe, Reginald (Box A-95, Folder 156)
    - Pierson, Edward (Box A-95, Folder 157)
    - Pierson, Nathaniel H. (Box A-95, Folder 158)
    - Pierson, Robert (Box A-95, Folder 159)
    - Pigott, Andesron J. (Box A-95, Folder 160)
    - Pigford, Richard (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 161)
    - Piggott, Bert (Box A-95, Folder 162)
    - Pilgrim, Carleton (Box A-95, Folder 163)
    - Pigler, Carole C. (Box A-95, Folder 164)
    - Pike, Max (Box A-95, Folder 165)
      Photographer if identified: James Pozark
    - Pike, O.B. (Box A-95, Folder 166)
    - Pike, Otis (Box A-95, Folder 167)
    - Pilate, Nathaniel (Box A-95, Folder 168)
    - Pilcher, James W. (Box A-95, Folder 169)
      Photographer if identified: James Pilcher
    - Pile, Edlynn (Box A-95, Folder 170)
    - Pile, Michael (Box A-95, Folder 171)
    - Pilgrim, Harold (Box A-95, Folder 172)
    - Pilgrim, Jill (Box A-95, Folder 173)
    - Pilgrim Jubilees, The (Box A-95, Folder 174)
    - Pilgrim, Louise (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 175)
    - Pilgrim, Robert C. (Box A-95, Folder 176)
    - Pilgrims, The (Box A-95, Folder 177)
    - Pilkington, Edward A. (Box A-95, Folder 178)
    - Pillay, Shonna (Box A-95, Folder 179)
    - Pilliam, Alfred J., Jr. (Box A-95, Folder 180)
    - Pills (Box A-95, Folder 181)
    - Pilots (Box A-95, Folder 182)
    - Pimbel, Christopher (Box A-95, Folder 183)
    - Pina, Samuel (Box A-95, Folder 184)
    - Pinado, Alan E. (Box A-95, Folder 185)
    - Pinch Hitters (Box A-95, Folder 186)
    - Pincham, Reginald (Box A-95, Folder 187)
    - Pinckney, Constance (Box A-95, Folder 188)
      Photographer if identified: Marc P. Anderson
    - Pinckney, David (Dr.) (Box A-95, Folder 189)
    - Pinckney, Darryl (Box A-95, Folder 190)
    - Pinckney, Lenore (Box A-95, Folder 191)
    - Pinckney, Napoleon (Prof.) (Box A-95, Folder 192)
    - Pinckney, Nathaniel (Box A-95, Folder 193)
    - Pinckney, Ross (Box A-95, Folder 194)
    - Pinkney, Leon (Box A-95, Folder 195)
    - Pinkney, Jerry (Box A-95, Folder 196)
    - Pinder, Enrique (Box A-95, Folder 197)
    - Pindling, Lynden Oscar (Box A-95, Folder 198)
      Approximately five prints with single-leaf typescript leaves affixed to verso with tape. Also one two-leaf typescript release.
      Photographer if identified: United Nations, Frederic Maura, Negro Press Photo Service Inc., Wide World Photos, Wm. (Gus) Roberts
    - Pindling, Lynden Oscar (Box A-95, Folder 199)
      Photographer if identified: Bahamas Ministry of Tourism/Frederic Maura
    - Pineview Convalescent Center (Box A-95, Folder 200)
      Also one three-leaf typescript release attached with staple through border.
    - Pinkard, Fred (Box A-95, Folder 201)
    - Pinkard, Norman T. (Box A-95, Folder 202)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene Photo
    - Pinkard, Mary D. (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 203)
    - Pinkett, Carole A. (Box A-95, Folder 204)
    - Pinkett, Flaxie Madison (Box A-95, Folder 205)
      Photographer if identified: Scurlock Studio, Harris & Ewing
    - Pinkett, Marcy (Box A-95, Folder 206)
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, Dave Greene
    - Pinkett, Mary (Box A-95, Folder 207)
    - Pinkett, Marcia (Box A-95, Folder 208)
    - Pinkney, Harold (Box A-95, Folder 209)
    - Pinkney, Mikall (Box A-95, Folder 210)
    - Pinkney, Nat (Box A-95, Folder 211)
      Photographer if identified: Leroy Henderson
    - Pinkney, Ron (Box A-95, Folder 212)
    - Pinkston, Anne (Box A-95, Folder 213)
    - Pinkston, Randall (Box A-95, Folder 214)
    - Pinkston, Walter C. (Box A-95, Folder 215)
      Also two leaves of cut-out newspaper clippings. Also one two-leaf typescript release.
    - Pinkston, Walter (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 216)
      Also one velox print. One print has newspaper clipping affixed to verso with tape.
      Photographer if identified: Jimmie Mannas, King Photographers
    - Pinn, Arnold E. (Box A-95, Folder 217)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers
    - Pinn, Peggy (Box A-95, Folder 218)
    - Pinn, Sam, Jr. (Box A-95, Folder 219)
    - Pinn, Walter S. (Rev.) (Box A-95, Folder 220)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Hayes, Harold T. Cooper
    - Pinn, Walter S. (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 221)
    - Pinn, Willard T. (Box A-95, Folder 222)
      One velox print
    - Pinnock, Theodore J. (Box A-95, Folder 223)
      Photographer if identified: Polk's Studio
    - Pinnock, Thomas (Box A-95, Folder 224)
      Photographer if identified: Rod Rodgers Dance Co.
    - Pino, E. (Box A-95, Folder 225)
    - "Pins and Needles" (Box A-95, Folder 226)
      Photographer if identified: Ronald Berger
    - Pinson, Billie (Box A-95, Folder 227)
    - Pinson, Vada (Box A-95, Folder 228)
      Photographer if identified: Cincinnati Reds Inc.
    - Pintchman, Charles (Box A-95, Folder 229)
      Photographer if identified: The Readers Digest
    - Pinter, Abraham (Box A-95, Folder 230)
      Also one business card, attached with paperclip.
    - Pinder, Frank D. (Box A-95, Folder 231)
      Prints are badly darkened with chemical stains
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Agency for International Development
    - Pinto, Buddy (Box A-95, Folder 232)
    - Pinza, Carla (Box A-95, Folder 233)
    - Pioneer Club of Portchester (Box A-95, Folder 234)
    - Pious, Robert (Box A-95, Folder 235)
    - "Pipe Dreams" (Box A-95, Folder 236)
    - "Pippin" (Box A-95, Folder 237)
    - Pisces Trio, The (Box A-95, Folder 238)
    - Pittman, Carlane (Box A-95, Folder 239)
    - Pittman, Raymond (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 240)
    - Pittman, Deborah (Box A-95, Folder 241)
    - Pittman, Elliana (Box A-95, Folder 242)
      Photographer if identified: Aurton Camargo Jr.
    - Pittman, Jean (Box A-95, Folder 243)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert
    - Pittman, Marcella (Box A-95, Folder 244)
    - Pittman, Noel (Box A-95, Folder 245)
    - Pittman, Portia (Box A-95, Folder 246)
      Photographer if identified: The White House
    - Pittman, Rita P. (Box A-95, Folder 247)
    - Pittman, Sample (Dr.) (Box A-95, Folder 248)
    - Pitts, Carolyn (Box A-95, Folder 249)
    - Pitts, Clarence (Box A-95, Folder 250)
      Photographer if identified: Freddie Wilson
    - Pitts, Cornelius C. (Box A-95, Folder 251)
    - Pitts, John L. (Box A-95, Folder 252)
      Photographer if identified: Victor B. Greene
    - Pitts, Lucius S. (Box A-95, Folder 253)
      Photographer if identified: Chris McNair Studio
    - Pits, Riley Leroy (Capt.) (Medal of Honor--Posthumous) (Box A-95, Folder 254)
    - Pitts, Robb (Box A-95, Folder 255)
    - Pitts, Theodore A. (Box A-95, Folder 256)
    - Pisces Unlimited, The (Box A-95, Folder 257)
      Photographer if identified: Rodriguez Photo
    - Pivots, The (Box A-95, Folder 258)
      Also one three-leaf ms. release.
    - Pizarro, Juan (Box A-95, Folder 259)
    - Plair, Ron (Box A-95, Folder 260)
    - Plants (Box A-95, Folder 261)
      Photographer if identified: Burpee Seeds
    - Plant, Richard L. (Box A-95, Folder 262)
      Photographer if identified: Tommy Weber
    - Plaskett, Eleana (Box A-95, Folder 263)
      Also one velox print. Also one photocopied three-leaf typescript cv.
    - Plaskett, Mel (Box A-95, Folder 264)
      Photographer if identified: Ed Eng
    - Platinum, Hook (Box A-95, Folder 265)
    - Platters (Box A-95, Folder 266)
    - Plant, Richard L. (Box A-95, Folder 267)
    - Playboy Bunnies (Box A-95, Folder 268)
    - Player, Willa (Box A-95, Folder 269)
    - Plaza Restaurant, The (Box A-95, Folder 270)
    - Plaza, Sheila (Box A-95, Folder 271)
    - Pleasant, Dorothy (Box A-95, Folder 272)
    - "Please Don't Cry and Say No" (Box A-95, Folder 273)
    - Pleasure (Box A-95, Folder 274)
    - Plinton, James O., Jr. (Box A-95, Folder 275)
      Photographer if identified: George Jervas Photo Studio
    - Plisemka, Gloria (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 276)
    - Plount, Colly (Box A-95, Folder 277)
      Photographer if identified: Jack Glass
    - Plummer, Berna (Box A-95, Folder 278)
    - Plummer, Doris (Box A-95, Folder 279)
    - Plummer, Edouard E. (Box A-95, Folder 280)
      Photographer if identified: Henry Monroe, Bro. David McAdams
    - Plummer, H.Z. (Bishop) (Box A-95, Folder 281)
    - Plummer, Viola (Box A-95, Folder 282)
    - Plunkett, Sherman (Box A-95, Folder 283)
    - Poache, Marcella (Box A-95, Folder 284)
    - Poag, Dean Thomas (Box A-95, Folder 285)
    - Poe, Charles W. (Box A-95, Folder 286)
    - Poets (Box A-95, Folder 287)
      One oversize print removed. Approximately six prints have tape residue stuck to the edges, rectos, and versos.
      Photographer if identified: Antonio Caballero-Marrero, Alex Summers, Larry Neilson, Pictorial Enterprise
      Number of Prints: 14
    - Poets (Box OS-1, Folder 2)
    - Pogue, David (Box A-95, Folder 288)
    - Pogue, Stephanie (Box A-95, Folder 289)
    - Poindexter, David (Box A-95, Folder 290)
    - Poindexter, Hildrus A. (Dr.) (Box A-95, Folder 291)
      Also one eight-leaf typescript release.
    - Poindexter, L. (Mrs.) (Box A-95, Folder 292)
    - Poindexter, Malcolm (Box A-95, Folder 293)
    - Point, Makea (Box A-95, Folder 294)
    - Pointer, Bonnie (Box A-96, Folder 1)
    - Pointer, Noel (Box A-96, Folder 2)
      Also one internegative and one velox print.
    - Pointer Sisters, The (Box A-96, Folder 3)
    - Poison (Box A-96, Folder 4)
    - Poison Tree (Box A-96, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: Barry Kramer/Jos. Abeles Studio
    - Poitier, Kingsley (Box A-96, Folder 6)
      Note on folder: " on picture with Wells, Glen."
    - Poitier, Pamela (Box A-96, Folder 7)
      Photographer if identified: Jim Wells
    - Poitier, Sandra (Box A-96, Folder 8)
    - Poitier, Sidney (Box A-96, Folder 9)
      Three prints stuck together. Also contains one press release.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, United Press International, Harris Photo, Manhattanville, Ralph Saunders, Wide World Photos, Glenn E. Tompkins
      Number of Prints: 31
    - Poitier, Sidney (Box A-96, Folder 10)
      Also one press release and one article (two typescript leaves).
      Photographer if identified: Lee Schecter/Barbara Schwei, United Press International, Sam Siegel/Metropolitan Photo Service, Harris Photo, Glenn E. Tompkins, Japan Air Lines, R.J. Fleming
      Number of Prints: 33
    - Poitier, Sidney (Box A-96, Folder 11)
      Note on folder: "born Feb. 20, 1927 in Miami Florida." Also one press release and five velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos, Cecil Layne, Leo Rosenthal, Roland Rose, Glenn E. Tompkins, United Press International, NMA Guinee, Chandler Studios, Lee Schecter/Barbara Schwei, Pictorial Enterprise, Angie Coqueran
      Number of Prints: 37
    - Poitier, Sidney (Mrs. Juanita) (Box A-96, Folder 12)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Bob Wands
    - Pokela, Nayati (Box A-96, Folder 13)
    - Polent, Lindsay (Box A-96, Folder 14)
    - Policano, Christopher (Box A-96, Folder 15)
    - Police - Arrests (Box A-96, Folder 16)
      Also five velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Lensman Photo, Bill Hayes
    - Police Athletic League (Box A-96, Folder 17)
      Five prints stuck together. Also contains one press release.
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert/News Voice International, A. Hansen, Bro. David McAdams, Photographic Unit NYC Transit Authority, Manning Solon, Harris Photo, Luigi
      Number of Prints: 32
    - Police Athletic League (Box A-96, Folder 18)
      Photographer if identified: T. Holmes
    - Police Athletic League N.Y.C. (Box A-96, Folder 19)
    - Police Brutality (Box A-96, Folder 20)
    - Police Brutality (Box A-96, Folder 21)
      One oversized item was removed.
    - Police Brutality (Box OS-1, Folder 2)
    - Police Brutality Hearings '83 (Box A-96, Folder 22)
    - Police - Cars (Box A-96, Folder 23)
      Two prints stuck together. Also contains two velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene, Harris Photo
    - Police - Ceremonies (Box A-96, Folder 24)
      Photographer if identified: Ralph Cooper, Harris Photo, New York City Housing Authority, Dave Greene, City of New York Dept. of Sanitation, Bill Mitchell, Willis E. Allen, Photographic Unit NYC Transit Authority, Bro. David McAdams
      Number of Prints: 38
    - Police (General) (Box A-96, Folder 25)
      Note on folder: "See also Transfile (Left side of gray bookcase)."
    - Police - Homicides (Box A-96, Folder 26)
    - Police Individual Photos (Box A-96, Folder 27)
      Twelve prints are Polaroids. Also contains five sketches and nine velox prints.
      Number of Prints: 34
    - Police Individual Photos (Box A-96, Folder 28)
      Also seven velox prints and one press release.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Spring 3100, Detective Al Young/Police Dept. Historian/Police Academy
    - Police Individual Photos (Box A-96, Folder 29)
      Four prints are Polaroids. Also twenty-one velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Bob Head
    - Police Individual Photos (Box A-96, Folder 30)
      One print is a Polaroid. Also three velox prints and one caption set in reverse.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Bob Head, Port Authority of NY & NJ, Pope's Studio
      Number of Prints: 35
    - Police Sketches (Box A-96, Folder 31)
      Three police sketches.
    - Police - Slain (Box A-96, Folder 32)
      Five prints are stuck together. Also three velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, NYC Housing Authority Photo Unit
    - Police Slay Victims, Relatives Remember (Box A-96, Folder 33)
      Note on folder: "(appear in) AM News 10/4/86."
    - Police Slaying of Blacks (Box A-96, Folder 34)
    - Police - Suspects + Wanted (Box A-96, Folder 35)
      Most prints are of police sketches. Two prints are Polaroids. Also four velox prints.
    - Police - 28th Precinct (Box A-96, Folder 36)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, George Cserna
    - Polier, Justine Wise (Judge) (Box A-96, Folder 37)
    - Polier, Shad + Justine (Box A-96, Folder 38)
    - Polite, James A. (Rev.) (Box A-96, Folder 39)
    - Polite, William (Rev.) (Box A-96, Folder 40)
    - Political Organization for Youths (Box A-96, Folder 41)
      Prints attached to two typescript leaves with paperclip.
    - Politicians (Box A-96, Folder 42)
      Note on folder: "see also Black Politicians." Also five velox prints and seven images cut from newspapers.
      Photographer if identified: Diana Mara Henry
    - Polk, George P. Jr. (Rev.) (Box A-96, Folder 43)
    - Polk, Janice (Box A-96, Folder 44)
      Note on folder: "See Lillian Polk."
    - Polk, John (Box A-96, Folder 45)
    - Polk, Lillian "Toy" (Box A-96, Folder 46)
    - Polk, Robert L. (Dr.) (Box A-96, Folder 47)
      Photographer if identified: Newell Johnson, Studio of the New York Times, Bill Anderson
    - Pollard, Diane (Box A-96, Folder 48)